<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. -->
    <string name="app_name">Tour Guide</string>
    <!--names that show in the tab views  -->
    <string name="tab1">Planets</string>
    <string name="tab2">Moons</string>
    <string name="tab3">Other objects</string>
    <!-- sun information -->
    <string name="sun">Sun</string>
    <!-- sun information will be added soon -->
    <!-- mercury information -->
    <string name="mercury">Mercury</string>
    <string name="mercury_text_box_1">
        The smallest planet in our solar system and nearest to the Sun, Mercury is only slightly
        larger than Earths Moon. From the surface of Mercury, the Sun would appear more than three
        times as large as it does when viewed from Earth, and the sunlight would be as much as 11
        times brighter. Despite its proximity to the Sun, Mercury is not the hottest planet in our
        solar system – that title belongs to nearby Venus, thanks to its dense atmosphere.
        But Mercury is the fastest planet, zipping around the Sun every 88 Earth days.
        Mercury is appropriately named for the swiftest of the ancient Roman gods.
    </string>
    <string name="mercury_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="mercury_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 1,516 miles (2,440 kilometers), Mercury is a little more than 1/3 the width
        of Earth. If Earth were the size of a nickel, Mercury would be about as big as a blueberry.
        From an average distance of 36 million miles (58 million kilometers), Mercury is 0.4
        astronomical units away from the Sun. One astronomical unit (abbreviated as AU), is the
        distance from the Sun to Earth. From this distance, it takes sunlight 3.2 minutes to travel
        from the Sun to Mercury.</string>
    <string name="mercury_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="mercury_text_box_5">
        Mercurys highly eccentric, egg-shaped orbit takes the planet as close as 29 million miles
        (47 million kilometers) and as far as 43 million miles (70 million kilometers) from the Sun.
        It speeds around the Sun every 88 days, traveling through space at nearly 29 miles
        (47 kilometers) per second, faster than any other planet. Mercury spins slowly on its axis
        and completes one rotation every 59 Earth days. But when Mercury is moving fastest in its
        elliptical orbit around the Sun (and it is closest to the Sun), each rotation is not
        accompanied by a sunrise and sunset like it is on most other planets. The morning Sun
        appears to rise briefly, set and rise again from some parts of the planet's surface. The
        same thing happens in reverse at sunset for other parts of the surface. One Mercury solar
        day (one full day-night cycle) equals 176 Earth days—just over two years on Mercury.
        Mercury's axis of rotation is tilted just 2 degrees with respect to the plane of its orbit
        around the Sun. That means it spins nearly perfectly upright and so does not experience
        seasons like many other planets do.
    </string>
    <string name="mercury_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="mercury_text_box_7">
        Mercury formed about 4.5 billion years ago when gravity pulled swirling gas and dust
        together to form this small planet nearest the Sun. Like its fellow terrestrial planets,
        Mercury has a central core, a rocky mantle and a solid crust.
    </string>
    <!-- venus information -->
    <string name="venus">Venus</string>
    <string name="venus_text_box_1">
        Venus is the second planet from the Sun and our closest planetary neighbor. Similar in
        structure and size to Earth, Venus spins slowly in the opposite direction from most planets.
        Its thick atmosphere traps heat in a runaway greenhouse effect, making it the hottest planet
        in our solar system with surface temperatures hot enough to melt lead. Glimpses below the
        clouds reveal volcanoes and deformed mountains. Venus is named for the ancient Roman goddess
        of love and beauty, who was known as Aphrodite to the Ancient Greeks.
    </string>
    <string name="venus_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="venus_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 3,760 miles (6,052 kilometers), Venus is roughly the same size as Earth —
        just slightly smaller. From an average distance of 67 million miles (108 million kilometers)
        , Venus is 0.7 astronomical units away from the Sun. One astronomical unit
        (abbreviated as AU), is the distance from the Sun to Earth. It takes sunlight 6 minutes to
        travel from the Sun to Venus.
    </string>
    <string name="venus_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="venus_text_box_5">
        Venus rotation and orbit are unusual in several ways. Venus is one of just two planets that
        rotate from east to west. Only Venus and Uranus have this "backwards" rotation. It completes
        one rotation in 243 Earth days — the longest day of any planet in our solar system, even
        longer than a whole year on Venus. But the Sun does not rise and set each "day" on Venus
        like it does on most other planets. On Venus, one day-night cycle takes 117 Earth days
        because Venus rotates in the direction opposite of its orbital revolution around the Sun.
        Venus makes a complete orbit around the Sun (a year in Venusian time) in 225 Earth days or
        slightly less than two Venusian day-night cycles. Its orbit around the Sun is the most
        circular of any planet — nearly a perfect circle. Other planet's orbits are more
        elliptical, or oval-shaped. With an axial tilt of just 3 degrees, Venus spins nearly
        upright, and so does not experience noticeable seasons.</string>
    <string name="venus_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="venus_text_box_7">
        When the solar system settled into its current layout about 4.5 billion years ago, Venus
        formed when gravity pulled swirling gas and dust together to form the second planet from
        the Sun. Like its fellow terrestrial planets, Venus has a central core, a rocky mantle and
        a solid crust.
    </string>
    <!-- earth information -->
    <string name="earth">Earth</string>
    <string name="earth_text_box_1">
        Our home planet is the third planet from the Sun, and the only place we know of so far
        that’s inhabited by living things. While Earth is only the fifth largest planet in the
        solar system, it is the only world in our solar system with liquid water on the surface.
        Just slightly larger than nearby Venus, Earth is the biggest of the four planets closest
        to the Sun, all of which are made of rock and metal. The name Earth is at least 1,000 years
        old. All of the planets, except for Earth, were named after Greek and Roman gods and
        goddesses. However, the name Earth is a Germanic word, which simply means “the ground.”
    </string>
    <string name="earth_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="earth_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 3,959 miles (6,371 kilometers), Earth is the biggest of the terrestrial
        planets, and the fifth largest planet overall. From an average distance of 93 million miles
        (150 million kilometers), Earth is exactly one astronomical unit away from the Sun because
        one astronomical unit (abbreviated as AU), is the distance from the Sun to Earth. This unit
        provides an easy way to quickly compare planets' distances from the Sun. It takes about
        eight minutes for light from the Sun to reach our planet.
    </string>
    <string name="earth_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="earth_text_box_5">
        As Earth orbits the Sun, it completes one rotation every 23.9 hours. It takes 365.25 days
        to complete one trip around the Sun. That extra quarter of a day presents a challenge to
        our calendar system, which counts one year as 365 days. To keep our yearly calendars
        consistent with our orbit around the Sun, every four years we add one day. That day is
        called a leap day, and the year its added to is called a leap year. Earths axis of
        rotation is tilted 23.4 degrees with respect to the plane of Earths orbit around the Sun.
        This tilt causes our yearly cycle of seasons. During part of the year, the northern
        hemisphere is tilted toward the Sun and the southern hemisphere is tilted away. With the Sun
        higher in the sky, solar heating is greater in the north producing summer there. Less
        direct solar heating produces winter in the south. Six months later, the situation is
        reversed. When spring and fall begin, both hemispheres receive roughly equal amounts of
        heat from the Sun.
    </string>
    <string name="earth_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="earth_text_box_7">
        When the solar system settled into its current layout about 4.5 billion years ago, Earth
        formed when gravity pulled swirling gas and dust in to become the third planet from the
        Sun. Like its fellow terrestrial planets, Earth has a central core, a rocky mantle and a
        solid crust.
    </string>
    <!-- mars information -->
    <string name="mars">Mars</string>
    <string name="mars_text_box_1">
        The fourth planet from the Sun, Mars is a dusty, cold, desert world with a very thin
        atmosphere. This dynamic planet has seasons, polar ice caps, extinct volcanoes, canyons
        and weather. Mars is one of the most explored bodies in our solar system, and its the only
        planet where we have sent rovers to roam the alien landscape. NASA missions have found lots
        of evidence that Mars was much wetter and warmer, with a thicker atmosphere, billions of
        years ago. Mars was named by the Romans for their god of war because its reddish color was
        reminiscent of blood. Other civilizations also named the planet for this attribute; for
        example, the Egyptians called it "Her Desher," meaning "the red one." Even today, it is
        frequently called the "Red Planet" because iron minerals in the Martian dirt oxidize, or
        rust, causing the surface to look red. A Martian Sunset On May 19th, 2005, NASA's Mars
        Exploration Rover Spirit captured this stunning view as the Sun sank below the rim of
        Gusev crater on Mars. Image Credit: NASA/JPL-Caltech/Texas A and M/Cornell
    </string>
    <string name="mars_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="mars_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 2,106 miles (3,390 kilometers), Mars is about half the size of Earth.
        If Earth were the size of a nickel, Mars would be about as big as a raspberry. From an
        average distance of 142 million miles (228 million kilometers), Mars is 1.5 astronomical
        units away from the Sun. One astronomical unit (abbreviated as AU), is the distance from
        the Sun to Earth. From this distance, it takes sunlight 13 minutes to travel from the Sun
        to Mars.
    </string>
    <string name="mars_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="mars_text_box_5">
        As Mars orbits the Sun, it completes one rotation every 24.6 hours, which is very similar
        to one day on Earth (23.9 hours). Martian days are called sols—short for "solar day." A
        year on Mars lasts 669.6 sols, which is the same as 687 Earth days. Mars axis of rotation
        is tilted 25 degrees with respect to the plane of its orbit around the Sun. This is another
        similarity with Earth, which has an axial tilt of 23.4 degrees. Like Earth, Mars has
        distinct seasons, but they last longer than seasons here on Earth since Mars takes longer
        to orbit the Sun (because it's farther away). And while here on Earth the seasons are evenly
        spread over the year, lasting 3 months (or one quarter of a year), on Mars the seasons vary
        in length because of Mars' elliptical, egg-shaped orbit around the Sun. Spring in the
        northern hemisphere (autumn in the southern) is the longest season at 194 sols. Autumn
        in the northern hemisphere (spring in the southern) is the shortest at 142 days. Northern
        winter/southern summer is 154 sols, and northern summer/southern winter is 178 sols.
    </string>
    <string name="mars_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="mars_text_box_7">
        When the solar system settled into its current layout about 4.5 billion years ago, Mars
        formed when gravity pulled swirling gas and dust in to become the fourth planet from the
        Sun. Mars is about half the size of Earth, and like its fellow terrestrial planets, it has
        a central core, a rocky mantle and a solid crust.
    </string>
    <!-- jupiter information -->
    <string name="jupiter">Jupiter</string>
    <string name="jupiter_text_box_1">
        Jupiter is the fifth planet from our Sun and is, by far, the largest planet in the solar
        system – more than twice as massive as all the other planets combined. Jupiters stripes and
        swirls are actually cold, windy clouds of ammonia and water, floating in an atmosphere of
        hydrogen and helium. Jupiter’s iconic Great Red Spot is a giant storm bigger than Earth
        that has raged for hundreds of years. Jupiter is surrounded by 79 known moons. Scientists
        are most interested in the Galilean satellites – the four largest moons discovered by
        Galileo Galilei in 1610: Io, Europa, Ganymede and Callisto. Jupiter also has several rings,
        but unlike the famous rings of Saturn, Jupiter’s rings are very faint and made of dust, not
        ice. Jupiter is named for the king of the ancient Roman gods.?
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="jupiter_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 43,440.7 miles (69,911 kilometers), Jupiter is 11 times wider than Earth.
        If Earth were the size of a nickel, Jupiter would be about as big as a basketball. From an
        average distance of 484 million miles (778 million kilometers), Jupiter is 5.2 astronomical
        units away from the Sun. One astronomical unit (abbreviated as AU), is the distance from
        the Sun to Earth. From this distance, it takes Sunlight 43 minutes to travel from the Sun
        to Jupiter.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="jupiter_text_box_5">
        Jupiter has the shortest day in the solar system. One day on Jupiter takes only about 10
        hours (the time it takes for Jupiter to rotate or spin around once), and Jupiter makes a
        complete orbit around the Sun (a year in Jovian time) in about 12 Earth years
        (4,333 Earth days). Its equator is tilted with respect to its orbital path around the Sun
        by just 3 degrees. This means Jupiter spins nearly upright and does not have seasons as
        extreme as other planets do.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="jupiter_text_box_7">
        Jupiter took shape when the rest of the solar system formed about 4.5 billion years ago,
        when gravity pulled swirling gas and dust in to become this gas giant. Jupiter took most of
        the mass left over after the formation of the Sun, ending up with more than twice the
        combined material of the other bodies in the solar system. In fact, Jupiter has the same
        ingredients as a star, but it did not grow massive enough to ignite. About 4 billion years
        ago, Jupiter settled into its current position in the outer solar system, where it is the
        fifth planet from the Sun.
    </string>
    <!-- saturn information -->
    <string name="saturn">Saturn</string>
    <string name="saturn_text_box_1">
        Saturn is the sixth planet from the Sun and the second largest planet in our solar system.
        Adorned with a dazzling system of icy rings, Saturn is unique among the planets. It is not
        the only planet to have rings, but none are as spectacular or as complex as Saturn. Like
        fellow gas giant Jupiter, Saturn is a massive ball made mostly of hydrogen and helium.
        Surrounded by more than 60 known moons, Saturn is home to some of the most fascinating
        landscapes in our solar system. From the jets of water that spray from Enceladus to the
        methane lakes on smoggy Titan, the Saturn system is a rich source of scientific discovery
        and still holds many mysteries. The farthest planet from Earth discovered by the unaided
        human eye, Saturn has been known since ancient times. The planet is named for the Roman god
        of agriculture and wealth, who was also the father of Jupiter.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="saturn_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 36,183.7 miles (58,232 kilometers), Saturn is 9 times wider than Earth.
        If Earth were the size of a nickel, Saturn would be about as big as a volleyball. From an
        average distance of 886 million miles (1.4 billion kilometers), Saturn is 9.5 astronomical
        units away from the Sun. One astronomical unit (abbreviated as AU), is the distance from
        the Sun to Earth. From this distance, it takes sunlight 80 minutes to travel from the Sun
        to Saturn.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="saturn_text_box_5">
        Saturn has the second-shortest day in the solar system. One day on Saturn takes only 10.7
        hours (the time it takes for Saturn to rotate or spin around once), and Saturn makes a
        complete orbit around the Sun (a year in Saturnian time) in about 29.4 Earth years (10,756
        Earth days). Its axis is tilted by 26.73 degrees with respect to its orbit around the Sun,
        which is similar to Earth's 23.5-degree tilt. This means that, like Earth, Saturn
        experiences seasons.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="saturn_text_box_7">
        Saturn took shape when the rest of the solar system formed about 4.5 billion years ago,
        when gravity pulled swirling gas and dust in to become this gas giant. About 4 billion
        years ago, Saturn settled into its current position in the outer solar system, where it
        is the sixth planet from the Sun. Like Jupiter, Saturn is mostly made of hydrogen and
        helium, the same two main components that make up the Sun.
    </string>
    <!-- uranus information -->
    <string name="uranus">Uranus</string>
    <string name="uranus_text_box_1">
        The seventh planet from the Sun with the third largest diameter in our solar system, Uranus
        is very cold and windy. The ice giant is surrounded by 13 faint rings and 27 small moons as
        it rotates at a nearly 90-degree angle from the plane of its orbit. This unique tilt makes
        Uranus appear to spin on its side, orbiting the Sun like a rolling ball. The first planet
        found with the aid of a telescope, Uranus was discovered in 1781 by astronomer William
        Herschel, although he originally thought it was either a comet or a star. It was two years
        later that the object was universally accepted as a new planet, in part because of
        observations by astronomer Johann Elert Bode. William Herschel tried unsuccessfully to name
        his discovery Georgium Sidus after King George III. Instead the planet was named for Uranus,
        the Greek god of the sky, as suggested by Johann Bode.
    </string>
    <string name="uranus_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="uranus_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 15,759.2 miles (25,362 kilometers), Uranus is 4 times wider than Earth. If
        Earth was the size of a nickel, Uranus would be about as big as a softball. From an average
        distance of 1.8 billion miles (2.9 billion kilometers), Uranus is 19.8 astronomical units
        away from the Sun. One astronomical unit (abbreviated as AU), is the distance from the Sun
        to Earth. From this distance, it takes sunlight 2 hours and 40 minutes to travel from the
        Sun to Uranus.
    </string>
    <string name="uranus_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="uranus_text_box_5">
        One day on Uranus takes about 17 hours (the time it takes for Uranus to rotate or spin
        once). And Uranus makes a complete orbit around the Sun (a year in Uranian time) in about
        84 Earth years (30,687 Earth days). Uranus is the only planet whose equator is nearly at a
        right angle to its orbit, with a tilt of 97.77 degrees—possibly the result of a collision
        with an Earth-sized object long ago. This unique tilt causes the most extreme seasons in the
        solar system. For nearly a quarter of each Uranian year, the Sun shines directly over each
        pole, plunging the other half of the planet into a 21-year-long, dark winter. Uranus is also
        one of just two planets that rotate in the opposite direction than most of the planets
        (Venus is the other one), from east to west.
    </string>
    <string name="uranus_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="uranus_text_box_7">
        Uranus took shape when the rest of the solar system formed about 4.5 billion years ago,
        when gravity pulled swirling gas and dust in to become this ice giant. Like its neighbor
        Neptune, Uranus likely formed closer to the Sun and moved to the outer solar system about
        4 billion years ago, where it is the seventh planet from the Sun.
    </string>
    <!-- neptune information -->
    <string name="neptune">Neptune</string>
    <string name="neptune_text_box_1">
        Dark, cold and whipped by supersonic winds, ice giant Neptune is the eighth and most distant
        planet in our solar system. More than 30 times as far from the Sun as Earth, Neptune is the
        only planet in our solar system not visible to the naked eye. In 2011 Neptune completed its
        first 165-year orbit since its discovery in 1846. Neptune is so far from the Sun that high
        noon on the big blue planet would seem like dim twilight to us. The warm light we see here
        on our home planet is roughly 900 times as bright as sunlight on Neptune. The ice giant
        Neptune was the first planet located through mathematical calculations. Using predictions
        made by Urbain Le Verrier, Johann Galle discovered the planet in 1846. The planet is named
        after the Roman god of the sea, as suggested by Le Verrier
    </string>
    <string name="neptune_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="neptune_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 15,299.4 miles (24,622 kilometers), Neptune is about four times wider than
        Earth. If Earth were the size of a nickel, Neptune would be about as big as a baseball.
        From an average distance of 2.8 billion miles (4.5 billion kilometers), Neptune is 30
        astronomical units away from the Sun. One astronomical unit (abbreviated as AU), is the
        distance from the Sun to Earth. From this distance, it takes sunlight 4 hours to travel
        from the Sun to Neptune
    </string>
    <string name="neptune_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="neptune_text_box_5">
        One day on Neptune takes about 16 hours (the time it takes for Neptune to rotate or spin
        once). And Neptune makes a complete orbit around the Sun (a year in Neptunian time) in
        about 165 Earth years (60,190 Earth days). Sometimes Neptune is even farther from the Sun
        than dwarf planet Pluto. Plutos highly eccentric, oval-shaped orbit brings it inside
        Neptunes orbit for a 20-year period every 248 Earth years. This switch, in which Pluto is
        closer to the Sun than Neptune, happened most recently from 1979 to 1999. Pluto can never
        crash into Neptune, though, because for every three laps Neptune takes around the Sun,
        Pluto makes two. This repeating pattern prevents close approaches of the two bodies.
        Neptune’s axis of rotation is tilted 28 degrees with respect to the plane of its orbit
        around the Sun, which is similar to the axial tilts of Mars and Earth. This means that
        Neptune experiences seasons just like we do on Earth; however, since its year is so long,
        each of the four seasons lasts for over 40 years
    </string>
    <string name="neptune_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="neptune_text_box_7">
        Neptune took shape when the rest of the solar system formed about 4.5 billion years ago,
        when gravity pulled swirling gas and dust in to become this ice giant. Like its neighbor
        Uranus, Neptune likely formed closer to the Sun and moved to the outer solar system about
        4 billion years ago.
    </string>
    <!-- end of planets -->
    <!-- start of moons -->
    <!-- earths moon information -->
    <string name="earth_moon">Moon</string>
    <string name="earth_moon_text_box_1">
        Earths Moon is the only place beyond Earth where humans have set foot, so far. The
        brightest and largest object in our night sky, the Moon makes Earth a more livable planet
        by moderating our home planets wobble on its axis, leading to a relatively stable climate.
        It also causes tides, creating a rhythm that has guided humans for thousands of years. The
        Moon was likely formed after a Mars-sized body collided with Earth several billion years
        ago. Earth's only natural satellite is simply called "the Moon" because people didn't know
        other moons existed until Galileo Galilei discovered four moons orbiting Jupiter in 1610.
        In Latin, the Moon was called Luna, which is the main adjective for all things
        Moon-related: lunar
    </string>
    <string name="earth_moon_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="earth_moon_text_box_3">
        With a radius of 1,079.6 miles (1,737.5 kilometers), the moon is less than a third the
        width of Earth. If Earth were the size of a nickel, the moon would be about as big as a
        coffee bean. The moon is farther away from Earth than most people realize. The moon is an
        average of 238,855 miles (384,400 kilometers) away. That means 30 Earth-sized planets could
        fit in between Earth and the moon. The moon is slowly moving away from Earth, getting about
        an inch farther away each year.
    </string>
    <string name="earth_moon_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="earth_moon_text_box_5">
        The moon is rotating at the same rate that it revolves around Earth (called synchronous
        rotation), so the same hemisphere faces Earth all the time. Some people call the far side
        and the hemisphere we never see from Earth the "dark side," but that is
        misleading. As the moon orbits Earth, different parts are in sunlight or darkness at
        different times. The changing illumination is why, from our perspective, the moon goes
        through phases. During a "full moon," the hemisphere of the moon we can see from Earth
        is fully illuminated by the sun. And a "new moon" occurs when the far side of the moon has
        full sunlight, and the side facing us is having its night. The moon makes a complete orbit
        around Earth in 27 Earth days and rotates or spins at that same rate, or in that same amount
        of time. Because Earth is moving as well  and rotating on its axis as it orbits the
        sun and from our perspective, the moon appears to orbit us every 29 days.
    </string>
    <string name="earth_moon_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="earth_moon_text_box_7">
        The leading theory of the moons origin is that a Mars-sized body collided with Earth about
        4.5 billion years ago. The resulting debris from both Earth and the impactor accumulated to
        form our natural satellite 239,000 miles (384,000 kilometers) away. The newly formed moon
        was in a molten state, but within about 100 million years, most of the global "magma ocean"
        had crystallized, with less-dense rocks floating upward and eventually forming the lunar crust.
    </string>
    <!-- mars moon deimos information -->
    <string name="mars_moon_deimos">Deimos</string>
    <string name="mars_moon_deimos_text_box_1">
        Asaph Hall was about to give up his frustrating search for a Martian moon one August night
        in 1877, but his wife Angelina urged him on. He discovered Deimos the next night, and
        Phobos six nights after that.
        Ninety-four years later, NASAs Mariner 9 spacecraft got a much better look at the two
        moons from its orbit around Mars. The dominant feature on Phobos, it found, was a crater
        six miles (10 kilometers) wide—nearly half the width of the moon itself. It was given
        Angelina's maiden name: Stickney.
    </string>
    <string name="mars_moon_deimos_text_box_2">Over View</string>
    <string name="mars_moon_deimos_text_box_3">
        Mars moons are among the smallest in the solar system. Phobos is a bit larger than Deimos,
        and orbits only 3,700 miles (6,000 kilometers) above the Martian surface. No known moon
        orbits closer to its planet. It whips around Mars three times a day, while the more distant
        Deimos takes 30 hours for each orbit. Phobos is gradually spiraling inward, drawing about
        six feet (1.8 meters) closer to the planet each century. Within 50 million years, it will
        either crash into Mars or break up and form a ring around the planet.
        To someone standing on the Mars-facing side of Phobos, Mars would take up a large part of
        the sky. And people may one day do just that. Scientists have discussed the possibility of
        using one of the Martian moons as a base from which astronauts could observe the Red Planet
        and launch robots to its surface, while shielded by miles of rock from cosmic rays and solar
        radiation for nearly two-thirds of every orbit.
        Like Earth's Moon, Phobos and Deimos always present the same face to their planet. Both are
        lumpy, heavily-cratered and covered in dust and loose rocks. They are among the darker
        objects in the solar system. The moons appear to be made of carbon-rich rock mixed with ice
        and may be captured asteroids.
        Phobos has only 1/1,000th as much gravitational pull as Earth. A 150-pound (68 kilogram)
        person would weigh two ounces (68 grams) there. Yet NASA's Mars Global Surveyor has shown
        evidence of landslides, and of boulders and dust that fell back down to the surface after
        being blasted off the moon by meteorites.
    </string>
    <string name="mars_moon_deimos_text_box_4">How They got there name</string>
    <string name="mars_moon_deimos_text_box_5">
        Hall named the moons for the mythological sons of Ares, the Greek counterpart of the Roman
        god, Mars. Phobos means fear or panic (think "phobia"), and Deimos means flight (as in
        running away after an overwhelming defeat). Fitting names for the sons of a war god
    </string>
    <string name="mars_moon_deimos_text_box_6">none</string>
    <string name="mars_moon_deimos_text_box_7">none</string>
    <!-- mars moon phobos information -->
    <string name="mars_moon_phobos">phobos</string>
    <string name="mars_moon_phobos_text_box_1">
        Asaph Hall was about to give up his frustrating search for a Martian moon one August night
        in 1877, but his wife Angelina urged him on. He discovered Deimos the next night, and
        Phobos six nights after that.
        Ninety-four years later, NASAs Mariner 9 spacecraft got a much better look at the two
        moons from its orbit around Mars. The dominant feature on Phobos, it found, was a crater
        six miles (10 kilometers) wide—nearly half the width of the moon itself. It was given
        Angelina's maiden name: Stickney.
    </string>
    <string name="mars_moon_phobos_text_box_2">Over View</string>
    <string name="mars_moon_phobos_text_box_3">
        Mars moons are among the smallest in the solar system. Phobos is a bit larger than Deimos,
        and orbits only 3,700 miles (6,000 kilometers) above the Martian surface. No known moon
        orbits closer to its planet. It whips around Mars three times a day, while the more distant
        Deimos takes 30 hours for each orbit. Phobos is gradually spiraling inward, drawing about
        six feet (1.8 meters) closer to the planet each century. Within 50 million years, it will
        either crash into Mars or break up and form a ring around the planet.
        To someone standing on the Mars-facing side of Phobos, Mars would take up a large part of
        the sky. And people may one day do just that. Scientists have discussed the possibility of
        using one of the Martian moons as a base from which astronauts could observe the Red Planet
        and launch robots to its surface, while shielded by miles of rock from cosmic rays and solar
        radiation for nearly two-thirds of every orbit.
        Like Earth's Moon, Phobos and Deimos always present the same face to their planet. Both are
        lumpy, heavily-cratered and covered in dust and loose rocks. They are among the darker
        objects in the solar system. The moons appear to be made of carbon-rich rock mixed with ice
        and may be captured asteroids.
        Phobos has only 1/1,000th as much gravitational pull as Earth. A 150-pound (68 kilogram)
        person would weigh two ounces (68 grams) there. Yet NASA's Mars Global Surveyor has shown
        evidence of landslides, and of boulders and dust that fell back down to the surface after
        being blasted off the moon by meteorites.
    </string>
    <string name="mars_moon_phobos_text_box_4">How They got there name</string>
    <string name="mars_moon_phobos_text_box_5">
        Hall named the moons for the mythological sons of Ares, the Greek counterpart of the Roman
        god, Mars. Phobos means fear or panic (think "phobia"), and Deimos means flight (as in
        running away after an overwhelming defeat). Fitting names for the sons of a war god
    </string>
    <string name="mars_moon_phobos_text_box_6">none</string>
    <string name="mars_moon_phobos_text_box_7">none</string>
    <!-- jupiter moon io information -->
    <string name="jupiter_moon_io">Io</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_io_text_box_1">
       The planet Jupiters four largest moons are called the Galilean satellites after Italian
        astronomer Galileo Galilei, who first observed them in 1610. The German astronomer Simon
        Marius claimed to have seen the moons around the same time, but he did not publish his
        observations and so Galileo is given the credit for their discovery. These large moons,
        named Io, Europa, Ganymede, and Callisto, are each distinctive worlds.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_io_text_box_2">Information</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_io_text_box_3">
       Io is the most volcanically active body in the solar system. Ios surface is covered by
        sulfur in different colorful forms. As Io travels in its slightly elliptical orbit,
        Jupiters immense gravity causes "tides" in the solid surface that rise 300 feet (100 meters)
        high on Io, generating enough heat for volcanic activity and to drive off any water. Io's
        volcanoes are driven by hot silicate magma.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_io_text_box_4">Structure</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_io_text_box_5">
        The interiors of Io, Europa and Ganymede have a layered structure (as does Earth). Io has a
        core, and a mantle of at least partially molten rock, topped by a crust of solid rock
        coated with sulfur compounds. Europa and Ganymede both have a core; a rock envelope around
        the core; a thick, soft ice layer; and a thin crust of impure water ice. In the case of
        Europa, a global subsurface water layer probably lies just below the icy crust. Layering at
        Callisto is less well defined and appears to be mainly a mixture of ice and rock.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_io_text_box_6">Moon Interactions</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_io_text_box_7">
        Three of the moons influence each other in an interesting way. Io is in a tug-of-war with
        Ganymede and Europa, and Europas orbital period (time to go around Jupiter once) is twice
        Ios period, and Ganymedes period is twice that of Europa. In other words, every time
        Ganymede goes around Jupiter once, Europa makes two orbits and Io makes four orbits. The
        moons all keep the same face towards Jupiter as they orbit, meaning that each moon turns
        once on its axis for every orbit around Jupiter.
    </string>
    <!-- jupiter moon Europa information -->
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Europa">Europa</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Europa_text_box_1">
       The planet Jupiters four largest moons are called the Galilean satellites after Italian
        astronomer Galileo Galilei, who first observed them in 1610. The German astronomer Simon
        Marius claimed to have seen the moons around the same time, but he did not publish his
        observations and so Galileo is given the credit for their discovery. These large moons,
        named Io, Europa, Ganymede, and Callisto, are each distinctive worlds.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Europa_text_box_2">Information</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Europa_text_box_3">
       Europas surface is mostly water ice, and there is evidence that it may be covering an ocean
        of water or slushy ice beneath. Europa is thought to have twice as much water as does Earth.
        This moon intrigues astrobiologists because of its potential for having a "habitable zone."
        Life forms have been found thriving near subterranean volcanoes on Earth and in other extreme
        locations that may be analogues to what may exist on Europa.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Europa_text_box_4">Structure</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Europa_text_box_5">
        The interiors of Io, Europa and Ganymede have a layered structure (as does Earth). Io has a
        core, and a mantle of at least partially molten rock, topped by a crust of solid rock coated
        with sulfur compounds. Europa and Ganymede both have a core; a rock envelope around the core;
        a thick, soft ice layer; and a thin crust of impure water ice. In the case of Europa, a
        global subsurface water layer probably lies just below the icy crust. Layering at Callisto
        is less well defined and appears to be mainly a mixture of ice and rock.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Europa_text_box_6">Moon Interactions</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Europa_text_box_7">
        Three of the moons influence each other in an interesting way. Io is in a tug-of-war with
        Ganymede and Europa, and Europas orbital period (time to go around Jupiter once) is twice
        Ios period, and Ganymedes period is twice that of Europa. In other words, every time
        Ganymede goes around Jupiter once, Europa makes two orbits and Io makes four orbits. The
        moons all keep the same face towards Jupiter as they orbit, meaning that each moon turns
        once on its axis for every orbit around Jupiter.
    </string>
    <!-- jupiter moon Ganymede information -->
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Ganymede">Ganymede</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Ganymede_text_box_1">
       The planet Jupiters four largest moons are called the Galilean satellites after Italian
        astronomer Galileo Galilei, who first observed them in 1610. The German astronomer Simon
        Marius claimed to have seen the moons around the same time, but he did not publish his
        observations and so Galileo is given the credit for their discovery. These large moons,
        named Io, Europa, Ganymede, and Callisto, are each distinctive worlds.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Ganymede_text_box_2">Information</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Ganymede_text_box_3">
       Ganymede is the largest moon in the solar system (larger than the planet Mercury), and is
        the only moon known to have its own internally generated magnetic field.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Ganymede_text_box_4">Structure</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Ganymede_text_box_5">
        The interiors of Io, Europa and Ganymede have a layered structure (as does Earth). Io has a
        core, and a mantle of at least partially molten rock, topped by a crust of solid rock coated
        with sulfur compounds. Europa and Ganymede both have a core; a rock envelope around the
        core; a thick, soft ice layer; and a thin crust of impure water ice. In the case of Europa,
        a global subsurface water layer probably lies just below the icy crust. Layering at Callisto
        is less well defined and appears to be mainly a mixture of ice and rock.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Ganymede_text_box_6">Moon Interactions</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Ganymede_text_box_7">
        Three of the moons influence each other in an interesting way. Io is in a tug-of-war with
        Ganymede and Europa, and Europas orbital period (time to go around Jupiter once) is twice
        Ios period, and Ganymedes period is twice that of Europa. In other words, every time
        Ganymede goes around Jupiter once, Europa makes two orbits and Io makes four orbits. The
        moons all keep the same face towards Jupiter as they orbit, meaning that each moon turns
        once on its axis for every orbit around Jupiter.
    </string>
    <!-- jupiter Callisto moon information -->
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Callisto">Callisto</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Callisto_text_box_1">
       The planet Jupiters four largest moons are called the Galilean satellites after Italian
        astronomer Galileo Galilei, who first observed them in 1610. The German astronomer Simon
        Marius claimed to have seen the moons around the same time, but he did not publish his
        observations and so Galileo is given the credit for their discovery. These large moons,
        named Io, Europa, Ganymede, and Callisto, are each distinctive worlds.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Callisto_text_box_2">Information</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Callisto_text_box_3">
       Callistos surface is extremely heavily cratered and ancient—a visible record of events from
        the early history of the solar system. However, the very few small craters on Callisto
        indicate a small degree of current surface activity.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Callisto_text_box_4">Structure</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Callisto_text_box_5">
        The interiors of Io, Europa and Ganymede have a layered structure (as does Earth). Io has a
        core, and a mantle of at least partially molten rock, topped by a crust of solid rock coated
        with sulfur compounds. Europa and Ganymede both have a core; a rock envelope around the
        core; a thick, soft ice layer; and a thin crust of impure water ice. In the case of Europa,
        a global subsurface water layer probably lies just below the icy crust. Layering at Callisto
        is less well defined and appears to be mainly a mixture of ice and rock.
    </string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Callisto_text_box_6">Moon Interactions</string>
    <string name="jupiter_moon_Callisto_text_box_7">
        Three of the moons influence each other in an interesting way. Io is in a tug-of-war with
        Ganymede and Europa, and Europas orbital period (time to go around Jupiter once) is twice
        Ios period, and Ganymedes period is twice that of Europa. In other words, every time
        Ganymede goes around Jupiter once, Europa makes two orbits and Io makes four orbits. The
        moons all keep the same face towards Jupiter as they orbit, meaning that each moon turns
        once on its axis for every orbit around Jupiter.
    </string>
    <!-- saturn moon Hyperion information -->
    <string name="saturn_moon_hyperion">Hyperion</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_hyperion_text_box_1">
        The Voyager and Pioneer flybys of the 1970s and 1980s provided rough sketches of Saturn’s
        moons. But during its many years in Saturn orbit, NASA’s Cassini spacecraft discovered
        previously unknown moons, solved mysteries about known ones, studied their interactions
        with the rings and uncovered new mysteries—including the discovery on an ocean moon with
        potential ingredients for life—that will engage a whole new generation of space scientists.
        While the larger moons are spherical, others are shaped like a sweet potato (Prometheus),
        a regular potato (Pandora), a meatball (Janus), and even a sponge (Hyperion). Some have a
        gnarled, irregular shape and texture like a dirty ice-ball (Epimetheus). One object observed
        in the rings (and unofficially called Peggy) may be a moon forming or disintegrating, or it
        might not truly be a moon at all. Four spacecraft have visited the Saturn system, but
        Cassini alone actually orbited the ringed planet. Doing so bought Cassini time—more than
        a decade—to linger and watch Saturn’s exotic zoo of 60-plus moons like no spacecraft
        before. Cassini looked, listened, sniffed and even tasted Saturn’s moons, and what it
        learned about them is nothing less than extraordinary.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_hyperion_text_box_2">Habitability Outside the Habitability Zone</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_hyperion_text_box_3">
        Haze-enshrouded Titan is Saturn’s largest moon and the solar system’s second-largest, and
        an all-around exceptional place. Titan is the only known world other than Earth where any
        sort of liquid collects on its surface.
        Earth has liquid water oceans because it orbits within the solar system’s habitable zone,
        the range of distance from our sun that is neither so hot that oceans boil away nor so cold
        that they’re frozen. The Saturn system is far outside of the habitable zone, and Titan’s
        surface temperature is so cold that the moon’s surface is largely water ice instead of
        rock. But the temperature is just right for liquid methane and ethane. Cassini scientists
        found not only that liquid methane and ethane exist on Titan, but that they rain from the
        sky and fill liquid lakes, which are as wide as several hundred miles (or kilometers) and
        as deep as hundreds of feet (or meters). Despite Titan’s distance from the sun, Cassini
        also found evidence of a global (or at least regional) liquid water ocean below its frigid
        surface, but Titan isn’t the only Saturnian moon that boasts of a subsurface sea.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_hyperion_text_box_4">Ocean Moon</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_hyperion_text_box_5">
        Cassini scientists were astonished when they found a plume spraying water vapor, icy
        particles and simple organic materials into space from the south polar region of Enceladus.
        Scientists determined that the jets are the source of material for Saturn’s E-Ring. The
        jets spew out of great fissures, or cracks, known as “tiger stripes,” which Cassini
        scientists found grow wider or narrower depending on where Enceladus is in its orbit
        around Saturn. Observations of its gravity and the contents of the plume suggested that
        Enceladus almost certainly contains a subsurface liquid water ocean near its southern
        polar region. Now more and more Cassini data indicates that Enceladus is home to a global
        (not just regional) ocean, and the jets near the south polar region are powered by
        hotspots, where heat from the interior ocean escapes. On Earth, hydrothermal vents at the
        ocean floor can produce habitats where organisms can flourish, completely cut off from
        sunlight. Many scientists suspect that life on Earth might have begun around these undersea
        environments. The evidence is beginning to pile up that Enceladus might have hydrothermal
        vents too. But vents or no vents, the Cassini mission showed that Enceladus appears to have
        all the components necessary for life. The food component is methane, which has been
        observed in surprising abundance in the plume, said Bonnie Buratti, a senior research
        scientist at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory. “Water, food, and heat—everything is there
        for life as we know it,” she said. “It’s all there.” Even if Enceladus isn’t home to even
        simple organisms, the presence of the necessary conditions is itself a remarkable finding.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_hyperion_text_box_6">Moon Mysteries Managed</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_hyperion_text_box_7">
        Enceladus and Titan get a lot of attention, but the Cassini mission also provided countless
        insights about dozens of Saturn’s other moons. The moon Mimas, whose Herschel Crater makes
        it look like the Death Star from "Star Wars," was thought to be an old, dead world,
        according to Cassini project scientist Linda Spilker. But Cassini scientists found
        evidence that it too may have a subsurface ocean, or at least a football-shaped water-ice
        core. “It’s curious. Mimas and Enceladus are the same size,” Spilker said, but Enceladus
        has water jets while Mimas appears not to. The reason for their differences is unknown.
        Cassini also found thin atmospheres around the moons Dione and Rhea—but we’re talking thin,
        around 5 trillion times less dense than at Earth’s surface. Hyperion can’t boast any sort of
        atmosphere, but the tumbling, sponge-looking moon does build up a static charge, which
        scientists realized when Cassini passed through a beam of electrons coming up from the
        moon’s surface. Hyperion is the only object in the solar system other than Earth’s moon
        that’s been confirmed as having a charged surface. Cassini also solved the centuries-old
        puzzle about why the moon Iapetus has one snow-white hemisphere while its other hemisphere
        is nearly as dark as charcoal. Iapetus is tidally locked, so it always shows the same side
        to Saturn, and one side always faces the direction in which it’s orbiting. It turns out that
        dark material falls on Iapetus’s leading side. “It’s coming actually from [the outer moon]
        Phoebe’s ring—it’s Phoebe dust,” Spilker said. The moon Phoebe creates one of Saturn’s
        rings, and Iapetus is flying through its debris. “Headed forward, you get all the bug
        splats,” Spilker said. At the same time, ice migrates to the poles, not by sliding but by
        sort of hopping, a molecule at a time. On the moon Tethys, Cassini observed mysterious red
        arcs, though they weren’t easy to see. “We didn’t even see them until a Cassini scientist
        started looking in the near-infrared,” Spilker said. In the infrared, the red arcs are
        obvious, as if someone dragged a giant red crayon across the surface of a golf ball. The
        arcs don’t appear to be related to any physical features of the moon’s surface, such as
        valleys or fractures. “They go up mountains and down into craters,” Spilker said. “But
        there’s no obvious fractures.” If the red arcs are coming from fractures, they’re too small
        to see at the resolution Cassini’s instruments provided. The arcs are also unevenly
        distributed on the moon’s surface. “It’s only the north,” Spilker said. “Why aren’t they in
        the south? It’s just sort of a late-mission mystery.” As scientists continue to analyze
        Cassini’s data, they will likely solve more mysteries about Saturn’s menagerie of moons,
        and they will almost certainly find more mysteries that need solving.
    </string>
    <!-- saturn moon laptus information -->
    <string name="saturn_moon_laptus">Laptus</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_laptus_text_box_1">
        The Voyager and Pioneer flybys of the 1970s and 1980s provided rough sketches of Saturn’s
        moons. But during its many years in Saturn orbit, NASA’s Cassini spacecraft discovered
        previously unknown moons, solved mysteries about known ones, studied their interactions
        with the rings and uncovered new mysteries—including the discovery on an ocean moon with
        potential ingredients for life—that will engage a whole new generation of space scientists.
        While the larger moons are spherical, others are shaped like a sweet potato (Prometheus),
        a regular potato (Pandora), a meatball (Janus), and even a sponge (Hyperion). Some have a
        gnarled, irregular shape and texture like a dirty ice-ball (Epimetheus). One object observed
        in the rings (and unofficially called Peggy) may be a moon forming or disintegrating, or it
        might not truly be a moon at all. Four spacecraft have visited the Saturn system, but
        Cassini alone actually orbited the ringed planet. Doing so bought Cassini time—more than
        a decade—to linger and watch Saturn’s exotic zoo of 60-plus moons like no spacecraft
        before. Cassini looked, listened, sniffed and even tasted Saturn’s moons, and what it
        learned about them is nothing less than extraordinary.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_laptus_text_box_2">Habitability Outside the Habitability Zone</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_laptus_text_box_3">
        Haze-enshrouded Titan is Saturn’s largest moon and the solar system’s second-largest, and
        an all-around exceptional place. Titan is the only known world other than Earth where any
        sort of liquid collects on its surface.
        Earth has liquid water oceans because it orbits within the solar system’s habitable zone,
        the range of distance from our sun that is neither so hot that oceans boil away nor so cold
        that they’re frozen. The Saturn system is far outside of the habitable zone, and Titan’s
        surface temperature is so cold that the moon’s surface is largely water ice instead of
        rock. But the temperature is just right for liquid methane and ethane. Cassini scientists
        found not only that liquid methane and ethane exist on Titan, but that they rain from the
        sky and fill liquid lakes, which are as wide as several hundred miles (or kilometers) and
        as deep as hundreds of feet (or meters). Despite Titan’s distance from the sun, Cassini
        also found evidence of a global (or at least regional) liquid water ocean below its frigid
        surface, but Titan isn’t the only Saturnian moon that boasts of a subsurface sea.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_laptus_text_box_4">Ocean Moon</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_laptus_text_box_5">
        Cassini scientists were astonished when they found a plume spraying water vapor, icy
        particles and simple organic materials into space from the south polar region of Enceladus.
        Scientists determined that the jets are the source of material for Saturn’s E-Ring. The
        jets spew out of great fissures, or cracks, known as “tiger stripes,” which Cassini
        scientists found grow wider or narrower depending on where Enceladus is in its orbit
        around Saturn. Observations of its gravity and the contents of the plume suggested that
        Enceladus almost certainly contains a subsurface liquid water ocean near its southern
        polar region. Now more and more Cassini data indicates that Enceladus is home to a global
        (not just regional) ocean, and the jets near the south polar region are powered by
        hotspots, where heat from the interior ocean escapes. On Earth, hydrothermal vents at the
        ocean floor can produce habitats where organisms can flourish, completely cut off from
        sunlight. Many scientists suspect that life on Earth might have begun around these undersea
        environments. The evidence is beginning to pile up that Enceladus might have hydrothermal
        vents too. But vents or no vents, the Cassini mission showed that Enceladus appears to have
        all the components necessary for life. The food component is methane, which has been
        observed in surprising abundance in the plume, said Bonnie Buratti, a senior research
        scientist at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory. “Water, food, and heat—everything is there
        for life as we know it,” she said. “It’s all there.” Even if Enceladus isn’t home to even
        simple organisms, the presence of the necessary conditions is itself a remarkable finding.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_laptus_text_box_6">Moon Mysteries Managed</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_laptus_text_box_7">
        Enceladus and Titan get a lot of attention, but the Cassini mission also provided countless
        insights about dozens of Saturn’s other moons. The moon Mimas, whose Herschel Crater makes
        it look like the Death Star from "Star Wars," was thought to be an old, dead world,
        according to Cassini project scientist Linda Spilker. But Cassini scientists found
        evidence that it too may have a subsurface ocean, or at least a football-shaped water-ice
        core. “It’s curious. Mimas and Enceladus are the same size,” Spilker said, but Enceladus
        has water jets while Mimas appears not to. The reason for their differences is unknown.
        Cassini also found thin atmospheres around the moons Dione and Rhea—but we’re talking thin,
        around 5 trillion times less dense than at Earth’s surface. Hyperion can’t boast any sort of
        atmosphere, but the tumbling, sponge-looking moon does build up a static charge, which
        scientists realized when Cassini passed through a beam of electrons coming up from the
        moon’s surface. Hyperion is the only object in the solar system other than Earth’s moon
        that’s been confirmed as having a charged surface. Cassini also solved the centuries-old
        puzzle about why the moon Iapetus has one snow-white hemisphere while its other hemisphere
        is nearly as dark as charcoal. Iapetus is tidally locked, so it always shows the same side
        to Saturn, and one side always faces the direction in which it’s orbiting. It turns out that
        dark material falls on Iapetus’s leading side. “It’s coming actually from [the outer moon]
        Phoebe’s ring—it’s Phoebe dust,” Spilker said. The moon Phoebe creates one of Saturn’s
        rings, and Iapetus is flying through its debris. “Headed forward, you get all the bug
        splats,” Spilker said. At the same time, ice migrates to the poles, not by sliding but by
        sort of hopping, a molecule at a time. On the moon Tethys, Cassini observed mysterious red
        arcs, though they weren’t easy to see. “We didn’t even see them until a Cassini scientist
        started looking in the near-infrared,” Spilker said. In the infrared, the red arcs are
        obvious, as if someone dragged a giant red crayon across the surface of a golf ball. The
        arcs don’t appear to be related to any physical features of the moon’s surface, such as
        valleys or fractures. “They go up mountains and down into craters,” Spilker said. “But
        there’s no obvious fractures.” If the red arcs are coming from fractures, they’re too small
        to see at the resolution Cassini’s instruments provided. The arcs are also unevenly
        distributed on the moon’s surface. “It’s only the north,” Spilker said. “Why aren’t they in
        the south? It’s just sort of a late-mission mystery.” As scientists continue to analyze
        Cassini’s data, they will likely solve more mysteries about Saturn’s menagerie of moons,
        and they will almost certainly find more mysteries that need solving.
    </string>
    <!-- saturn moon mimas information -->
    <string name="saturn_moon_mimas">Mimas</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_mimas_text_box_1">
        The Voyager and Pioneer flybys of the 1970s and 1980s provided rough sketches of Saturn’s
        moons. But during its many years in Saturn orbit, NASA’s Cassini spacecraft discovered
        previously unknown moons, solved mysteries about known ones, studied their interactions
        with the rings and uncovered new mysteries—including the discovery on an ocean moon with
        potential ingredients for life—that will engage a whole new generation of space scientists.
        While the larger moons are spherical, others are shaped like a sweet potato (Prometheus),
        a regular potato (Pandora), a meatball (Janus), and even a sponge (Hyperion). Some have a
        gnarled, irregular shape and texture like a dirty ice-ball (Epimetheus). One object observed
        in the rings (and unofficially called Peggy) may be a moon forming or disintegrating, or it
        might not truly be a moon at all. Four spacecraft have visited the Saturn system, but
        Cassini alone actually orbited the ringed planet. Doing so bought Cassini time—more than
        a decade—to linger and watch Saturn’s exotic zoo of 60-plus moons like no spacecraft
        before. Cassini looked, listened, sniffed and even tasted Saturn’s moons, and what it
        learned about them is nothing less than extraordinary.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_mimas_text_box_2">Habitability Outside the Habitability Zone</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_mimas_text_box_3">
        Haze-enshrouded Titan is Saturn’s largest moon and the solar system’s second-largest, and
        an all-around exceptional place. Titan is the only known world other than Earth where any
        sort of liquid collects on its surface.
        Earth has liquid water oceans because it orbits within the solar system’s habitable zone,
        the range of distance from our sun that is neither so hot that oceans boil away nor so cold
        that they’re frozen. The Saturn system is far outside of the habitable zone, and Titan’s
        surface temperature is so cold that the moon’s surface is largely water ice instead of
        rock. But the temperature is just right for liquid methane and ethane. Cassini scientists
        found not only that liquid methane and ethane exist on Titan, but that they rain from the
        sky and fill liquid lakes, which are as wide as several hundred miles (or kilometers) and
        as deep as hundreds of feet (or meters). Despite Titan’s distance from the sun, Cassini
        also found evidence of a global (or at least regional) liquid water ocean below its frigid
        surface, but Titan isn’t the only Saturnian moon that boasts of a subsurface sea.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_mimas_text_box_4">Ocean Moon</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_mimas_text_box_5">
        Cassini scientists were astonished when they found a plume spraying water vapor, icy
        particles and simple organic materials into space from the south polar region of Enceladus.
        Scientists determined that the jets are the source of material for Saturn’s E-Ring. The
        jets spew out of great fissures, or cracks, known as “tiger stripes,” which Cassini
        scientists found grow wider or narrower depending on where Enceladus is in its orbit
        around Saturn. Observations of its gravity and the contents of the plume suggested that
        Enceladus almost certainly contains a subsurface liquid water ocean near its southern
        polar region. Now more and more Cassini data indicates that Enceladus is home to a global
        (not just regional) ocean, and the jets near the south polar region are powered by
        hotspots, where heat from the interior ocean escapes. On Earth, hydrothermal vents at the
        ocean floor can produce habitats where organisms can flourish, completely cut off from
        sunlight. Many scientists suspect that life on Earth might have begun around these undersea
        environments. The evidence is beginning to pile up that Enceladus might have hydrothermal
        vents too. But vents or no vents, the Cassini mission showed that Enceladus appears to have
        all the components necessary for life. The food component is methane, which has been
        observed in surprising abundance in the plume, said Bonnie Buratti, a senior research
        scientist at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory. “Water, food, and heat—everything is there
        for life as we know it,” she said. “It’s all there.” Even if Enceladus isn’t home to even
        simple organisms, the presence of the necessary conditions is itself a remarkable finding.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_mimas_text_box_6">Moon Mysteries Managed</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_mimas_text_box_7">
        Enceladus and Titan get a lot of attention, but the Cassini mission also provided countless
        insights about dozens of Saturn’s other moons. The moon Mimas, whose Herschel Crater makes
        it look like the Death Star from "Star Wars," was thought to be an old, dead world,
        according to Cassini project scientist Linda Spilker. But Cassini scientists found
        evidence that it too may have a subsurface ocean, or at least a football-shaped water-ice
        core. “It’s curious. Mimas and Enceladus are the same size,” Spilker said, but Enceladus
        has water jets while Mimas appears not to. The reason for their differences is unknown.
        Cassini also found thin atmospheres around the moons Dione and Rhea—but we’re talking thin,
        around 5 trillion times less dense than at Earth’s surface. Hyperion can’t boast any sort of
        atmosphere, but the tumbling, sponge-looking moon does build up a static charge, which
        scientists realized when Cassini passed through a beam of electrons coming up from the
        moon’s surface. Hyperion is the only object in the solar system other than Earth’s moon
        that’s been confirmed as having a charged surface. Cassini also solved the centuries-old
        puzzle about why the moon Iapetus has one snow-white hemisphere while its other hemisphere
        is nearly as dark as charcoal. Iapetus is tidally locked, so it always shows the same side
        to Saturn, and one side always faces the direction in which it’s orbiting. It turns out that
        dark material falls on Iapetus’s leading side. “It’s coming actually from [the outer moon]
        Phoebe’s ring—it’s Phoebe dust,” Spilker said. The moon Phoebe creates one of Saturn’s
        rings, and Iapetus is flying through its debris. “Headed forward, you get all the bug
        splats,” Spilker said. At the same time, ice migrates to the poles, not by sliding but by
        sort of hopping, a molecule at a time. On the moon Tethys, Cassini observed mysterious red
        arcs, though they weren’t easy to see. “We didn’t even see them until a Cassini scientist
        started looking in the near-infrared,” Spilker said. In the infrared, the red arcs are
        obvious, as if someone dragged a giant red crayon across the surface of a golf ball. The
        arcs don’t appear to be related to any physical features of the moon’s surface, such as
        valleys or fractures. “They go up mountains and down into craters,” Spilker said. “But
        there’s no obvious fractures.” If the red arcs are coming from fractures, they’re too small
        to see at the resolution Cassini’s instruments provided. The arcs are also unevenly
        distributed on the moon’s surface. “It’s only the north,” Spilker said. “Why aren’t they in
        the south? It’s just sort of a late-mission mystery.” As scientists continue to analyze
        Cassini’s data, they will likely solve more mysteries about Saturn’s menagerie of moons,
        and they will almost certainly find more mysteries that need solving.
    </string>
    <!-- saturn moon rhea information -->
    <string name="saturn_moon_rhea">Rhea</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_rhea_text_box_1">
        The Voyager and Pioneer flybys of the 1970s and 1980s provided rough sketches of Saturn’s
        moons. But during its many years in Saturn orbit, NASA’s Cassini spacecraft discovered
        previously unknown moons, solved mysteries about known ones, studied their interactions
        with the rings and uncovered new mysteries—including the discovery on an ocean moon with
        potential ingredients for life—that will engage a whole new generation of space scientists.
        While the larger moons are spherical, others are shaped like a sweet potato (Prometheus),
        a regular potato (Pandora), a meatball (Janus), and even a sponge (Hyperion). Some have a
        gnarled, irregular shape and texture like a dirty ice-ball (Epimetheus). One object observed
        in the rings (and unofficially called Peggy) may be a moon forming or disintegrating, or it
        might not truly be a moon at all. Four spacecraft have visited the Saturn system, but
        Cassini alone actually orbited the ringed planet. Doing so bought Cassini time—more than
        a decade—to linger and watch Saturn’s exotic zoo of 60-plus moons like no spacecraft
        before. Cassini looked, listened, sniffed and even tasted Saturn’s moons, and what it
        learned about them is nothing less than extraordinary.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_rhea_text_box_2">Habitability Outside the Habitability Zone</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_rhea_text_box_3">
        Haze-enshrouded Titan is Saturn’s largest moon and the solar system’s second-largest, and
        an all-around exceptional place. Titan is the only known world other than Earth where any
        sort of liquid collects on its surface.
        Earth has liquid water oceans because it orbits within the solar system’s habitable zone,
        the range of distance from our sun that is neither so hot that oceans boil away nor so cold
        that they’re frozen. The Saturn system is far outside of the habitable zone, and Titan’s
        surface temperature is so cold that the moon’s surface is largely water ice instead of
        rock. But the temperature is just right for liquid methane and ethane. Cassini scientists
        found not only that liquid methane and ethane exist on Titan, but that they rain from the
        sky and fill liquid lakes, which are as wide as several hundred miles (or kilometers) and
        as deep as hundreds of feet (or meters). Despite Titan’s distance from the sun, Cassini
        also found evidence of a global (or at least regional) liquid water ocean below its frigid
        surface, but Titan isn’t the only Saturnian moon that boasts of a subsurface sea.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_rhea_text_box_4">Ocean Moon</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_rhea_text_box_5">
        Cassini scientists were astonished when they found a plume spraying water vapor, icy
        particles and simple organic materials into space from the south polar region of Enceladus.
        Scientists determined that the jets are the source of material for Saturn’s E-Ring. The
        jets spew out of great fissures, or cracks, known as “tiger stripes,” which Cassini
        scientists found grow wider or narrower depending on where Enceladus is in its orbit
        around Saturn. Observations of its gravity and the contents of the plume suggested that
        Enceladus almost certainly contains a subsurface liquid water ocean near its southern
        polar region. Now more and more Cassini data indicates that Enceladus is home to a global
        (not just regional) ocean, and the jets near the south polar region are powered by
        hotspots, where heat from the interior ocean escapes. On Earth, hydrothermal vents at the
        ocean floor can produce habitats where organisms can flourish, completely cut off from
        sunlight. Many scientists suspect that life on Earth might have begun around these undersea
        environments. The evidence is beginning to pile up that Enceladus might have hydrothermal
        vents too. But vents or no vents, the Cassini mission showed that Enceladus appears to have
        all the components necessary for life. The food component is methane, which has been
        observed in surprising abundance in the plume, said Bonnie Buratti, a senior research
        scientist at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory. “Water, food, and heat—everything is there
        for life as we know it,” she said. “It’s all there.” Even if Enceladus isn’t home to even
        simple organisms, the presence of the necessary conditions is itself a remarkable finding.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_rhea_text_box_6">Moon Mysteries Managed</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_rhea_text_box_7">
        Enceladus and Titan get a lot of attention, but the Cassini mission also provided countless
        insights about dozens of Saturn’s other moons. The moon Mimas, whose Herschel Crater makes
        it look like the Death Star from "Star Wars," was thought to be an old, dead world,
        according to Cassini project scientist Linda Spilker. But Cassini scientists found
        evidence that it too may have a subsurface ocean, or at least a football-shaped water-ice
        core. “It’s curious. Mimas and Enceladus are the same size,” Spilker said, but Enceladus
        has water jets while Mimas appears not to. The reason for their differences is unknown.
        Cassini also found thin atmospheres around the moons Dione and Rhea—but we’re talking thin,
        around 5 trillion times less dense than at Earth’s surface. Hyperion can’t boast any sort of
        atmosphere, but the tumbling, sponge-looking moon does build up a static charge, which
        scientists realized when Cassini passed through a beam of electrons coming up from the
        moon’s surface. Hyperion is the only object in the solar system other than Earth’s moon
        that’s been confirmed as having a charged surface. Cassini also solved the centuries-old
        puzzle about why the moon Iapetus has one snow-white hemisphere while its other hemisphere
        is nearly as dark as charcoal. Iapetus is tidally locked, so it always shows the same side
        to Saturn, and one side always faces the direction in which it’s orbiting. It turns out that
        dark material falls on Iapetus’s leading side. “It’s coming actually from [the outer moon]
        Phoebe’s ring—it’s Phoebe dust,” Spilker said. The moon Phoebe creates one of Saturn’s
        rings, and Iapetus is flying through its debris. “Headed forward, you get all the bug
        splats,” Spilker said. At the same time, ice migrates to the poles, not by sliding but by
        sort of hopping, a molecule at a time. On the moon Tethys, Cassini observed mysterious red
        arcs, though they weren’t easy to see. “We didn’t even see them until a Cassini scientist
        started looking in the near-infrared,” Spilker said. In the infrared, the red arcs are
        obvious, as if someone dragged a giant red crayon across the surface of a golf ball. The
        arcs don’t appear to be related to any physical features of the moon’s surface, such as
        valleys or fractures. “They go up mountains and down into craters,” Spilker said. “But
        there’s no obvious fractures.” If the red arcs are coming from fractures, they’re too small
        to see at the resolution Cassini’s instruments provided. The arcs are also unevenly
        distributed on the moon’s surface. “It’s only the north,” Spilker said. “Why aren’t they in
        the south? It’s just sort of a late-mission mystery.” As scientists continue to analyze
        Cassini’s data, they will likely solve more mysteries about Saturn’s menagerie of moons,
        and they will almost certainly find more mysteries that need solving.
    </string>
    <!-- saturn moon thtys information -->
    <string name="saturn_moon_thtys">Thtys</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_thtys_text_box_1">
        The Voyager and Pioneer flybys of the 1970s and 1980s provided rough sketches of Saturn’s
        moons. But during its many years in Saturn orbit, NASA’s Cassini spacecraft discovered
        previously unknown moons, solved mysteries about known ones, studied their interactions
        with the rings and uncovered new mysteries—including the discovery on an ocean moon with
        potential ingredients for life—that will engage a whole new generation of space scientists.
        While the larger moons are spherical, others are shaped like a sweet potato (Prometheus),
        a regular potato (Pandora), a meatball (Janus), and even a sponge (Hyperion). Some have a
        gnarled, irregular shape and texture like a dirty ice-ball (Epimetheus). One object observed
        in the rings (and unofficially called Peggy) may be a moon forming or disintegrating, or it
        might not truly be a moon at all. Four spacecraft have visited the Saturn system, but
        Cassini alone actually orbited the ringed planet. Doing so bought Cassini time—more than
        a decade—to linger and watch Saturn’s exotic zoo of 60-plus moons like no spacecraft
        before. Cassini looked, listened, sniffed and even tasted Saturn’s moons, and what it
        learned about them is nothing less than extraordinary.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_thtys_text_box_2">Habitability Outside the Habitability Zone</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_thtys_text_box_3">
        Haze-enshrouded Titan is Saturn’s largest moon and the solar system’s second-largest, and
        an all-around exceptional place. Titan is the only known world other than Earth where any
        sort of liquid collects on its surface.
        Earth has liquid water oceans because it orbits within the solar system’s habitable zone,
        the range of distance from our sun that is neither so hot that oceans boil away nor so cold
        that they’re frozen. The Saturn system is far outside of the habitable zone, and Titan’s
        surface temperature is so cold that the moon’s surface is largely water ice instead of
        rock. But the temperature is just right for liquid methane and ethane. Cassini scientists
        found not only that liquid methane and ethane exist on Titan, but that they rain from the
        sky and fill liquid lakes, which are as wide as several hundred miles (or kilometers) and
        as deep as hundreds of feet (or meters). Despite Titan’s distance from the sun, Cassini
        also found evidence of a global (or at least regional) liquid water ocean below its frigid
        surface, but Titan isn’t the only Saturnian moon that boasts of a subsurface sea.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_thtys_text_box_4">Ocean Moon</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_thtys_text_box_5">
        Cassini scientists were astonished when they found a plume spraying water vapor, icy
        particles and simple organic materials into space from the south polar region of Enceladus.
        Scientists determined that the jets are the source of material for Saturn’s E-Ring. The
        jets spew out of great fissures, or cracks, known as “tiger stripes,” which Cassini
        scientists found grow wider or narrower depending on where Enceladus is in its orbit
        around Saturn. Observations of its gravity and the contents of the plume suggested that
        Enceladus almost certainly contains a subsurface liquid water ocean near its southern
        polar region. Now more and more Cassini data indicates that Enceladus is home to a global
        (not just regional) ocean, and the jets near the south polar region are powered by
        hotspots, where heat from the interior ocean escapes. On Earth, hydrothermal vents at the
        ocean floor can produce habitats where organisms can flourish, completely cut off from
        sunlight. Many scientists suspect that life on Earth might have begun around these undersea
        environments. The evidence is beginning to pile up that Enceladus might have hydrothermal
        vents too. But vents or no vents, the Cassini mission showed that Enceladus appears to have
        all the components necessary for life. The food component is methane, which has been
        observed in surprising abundance in the plume, said Bonnie Buratti, a senior research
        scientist at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory. “Water, food, and heat—everything is there
        for life as we know it,” she said. “It’s all there.” Even if Enceladus isn’t home to even
        simple organisms, the presence of the necessary conditions is itself a remarkable finding.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_thtys_text_box_6">Moon Mysteries Managed</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_thtys_text_box_7">
        Enceladus and Titan get a lot of attention, but the Cassini mission also provided countless
        insights about dozens of Saturn’s other moons. The moon Mimas, whose Herschel Crater makes
        it look like the Death Star from "Star Wars," was thought to be an old, dead world,
        according to Cassini project scientist Linda Spilker. But Cassini scientists found
        evidence that it too may have a subsurface ocean, or at least a football-shaped water-ice
        core. “It’s curious. Mimas and Enceladus are the same size,” Spilker said, but Enceladus
        has water jets while Mimas appears not to. The reason for their differences is unknown.
        Cassini also found thin atmospheres around the moons Dione and Rhea—but we’re talking thin,
        around 5 trillion times less dense than at Earth’s surface. Hyperion can’t boast any sort of
        atmosphere, but the tumbling, sponge-looking moon does build up a static charge, which
        scientists realized when Cassini passed through a beam of electrons coming up from the
        moon’s surface. Hyperion is the only object in the solar system other than Earth’s moon
        that’s been confirmed as having a charged surface. Cassini also solved the centuries-old
        puzzle about why the moon Iapetus has one snow-white hemisphere while its other hemisphere
        is nearly as dark as charcoal. Iapetus is tidally locked, so it always shows the same side
        to Saturn, and one side always faces the direction in which it’s orbiting. It turns out that
        dark material falls on Iapetus’s leading side. “It’s coming actually from [the outer moon]
        Phoebe’s ring—it’s Phoebe dust,” Spilker said. The moon Phoebe creates one of Saturn’s
        rings, and Iapetus is flying through its debris. “Headed forward, you get all the bug
        splats,” Spilker said. At the same time, ice migrates to the poles, not by sliding but by
        sort of hopping, a molecule at a time. On the moon Tethys, Cassini observed mysterious red
        arcs, though they weren’t easy to see. “We didn’t even see them until a Cassini scientist
        started looking in the near-infrared,” Spilker said. In the infrared, the red arcs are
        obvious, as if someone dragged a giant red crayon across the surface of a golf ball. The
        arcs don’t appear to be related to any physical features of the moon’s surface, such as
        valleys or fractures. “They go up mountains and down into craters,” Spilker said. “But
        there’s no obvious fractures.” If the red arcs are coming from fractures, they’re too small
        to see at the resolution Cassini’s instruments provided. The arcs are also unevenly
        distributed on the moon’s surface. “It’s only the north,” Spilker said. “Why aren’t they in
        the south? It’s just sort of a late-mission mystery.” As scientists continue to analyze
        Cassini’s data, they will likely solve more mysteries about Saturn’s menagerie of moons,
        and they will almost certainly find more mysteries that need solving.
    </string>
    <!-- saturn moon triton information -->
    <string name="saturn_moon_triton">Triton</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_triton_text_box_1">
        The Voyager and Pioneer flybys of the 1970s and 1980s provided rough sketches of Saturn’s
        moons. But during its many years in Saturn orbit, NASA’s Cassini spacecraft discovered
        previously unknown moons, solved mysteries about known ones, studied their interactions
        with the rings and uncovered new mysteries—including the discovery on an ocean moon with
        potential ingredients for life—that will engage a whole new generation of space scientists.
        While the larger moons are spherical, others are shaped like a sweet potato (Prometheus),
        a regular potato (Pandora), a meatball (Janus), and even a sponge (Hyperion). Some have a
        gnarled, irregular shape and texture like a dirty ice-ball (Epimetheus). One object observed
        in the rings (and unofficially called Peggy) may be a moon forming or disintegrating, or it
        might not truly be a moon at all. Four spacecraft have visited the Saturn system, but
        Cassini alone actually orbited the ringed planet. Doing so bought Cassini time—more than
        a decade—to linger and watch Saturn’s exotic zoo of 60-plus moons like no spacecraft
        before. Cassini looked, listened, sniffed and even tasted Saturn’s moons, and what it
        learned about them is nothing less than extraordinary.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_triton_text_box_2">Habitability Outside the Habitability Zone</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_triton_text_box_3">
        Haze-enshrouded Titan is Saturn’s largest moon and the solar system’s second-largest, and
        an all-around exceptional place. Titan is the only known world other than Earth where any
        sort of liquid collects on its surface.
        Earth has liquid water oceans because it orbits within the solar system’s habitable zone,
        the range of distance from our sun that is neither so hot that oceans boil away nor so cold
        that they’re frozen. The Saturn system is far outside of the habitable zone, and Titan’s
        surface temperature is so cold that the moon’s surface is largely water ice instead of
        rock. But the temperature is just right for liquid methane and ethane. Cassini scientists
        found not only that liquid methane and ethane exist on Titan, but that they rain from the
        sky and fill liquid lakes, which are as wide as several hundred miles (or kilometers) and
        as deep as hundreds of feet (or meters). Despite Titan’s distance from the sun, Cassini
        also found evidence of a global (or at least regional) liquid water ocean below its frigid
        surface, but Titan isn’t the only Saturnian moon that boasts of a subsurface sea.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_triton_text_box_4">Ocean Moon</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_triton_text_box_5">
        Cassini scientists were astonished when they found a plume spraying water vapor, icy
        particles and simple organic materials into space from the south polar region of Enceladus.
        Scientists determined that the jets are the source of material for Saturn’s E-Ring. The
        jets spew out of great fissures, or cracks, known as “tiger stripes,” which Cassini
        scientists found grow wider or narrower depending on where Enceladus is in its orbit
        around Saturn. Observations of its gravity and the contents of the plume suggested that
        Enceladus almost certainly contains a subsurface liquid water ocean near its southern
        polar region. Now more and more Cassini data indicates that Enceladus is home to a global
        (not just regional) ocean, and the jets near the south polar region are powered by
        hotspots, where heat from the interior ocean escapes. On Earth, hydrothermal vents at the
        ocean floor can produce habitats where organisms can flourish, completely cut off from
        sunlight. Many scientists suspect that life on Earth might have begun around these undersea
        environments. The evidence is beginning to pile up that Enceladus might have hydrothermal
        vents too. But vents or no vents, the Cassini mission showed that Enceladus appears to have
        all the components necessary for life. The food component is methane, which has been
        observed in surprising abundance in the plume, said Bonnie Buratti, a senior research
        scientist at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory. “Water, food, and heat—everything is there
        for life as we know it,” she said. “It’s all there.” Even if Enceladus isn’t home to even
        simple organisms, the presence of the necessary conditions is itself a remarkable finding.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_triton_text_box_6">Moon Mysteries Managed</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_triton_text_box_7">
        Enceladus and Titan get a lot of attention, but the Cassini mission also provided countless
        insights about dozens of Saturn’s other moons. The moon Mimas, whose Herschel Crater makes
        it look like the Death Star from "Star Wars," was thought to be an old, dead world,
        according to Cassini project scientist Linda Spilker. But Cassini scientists found
        evidence that it too may have a subsurface ocean, or at least a football-shaped water-ice
        core. “It’s curious. Mimas and Enceladus are the same size,” Spilker said, but Enceladus
        has water jets while Mimas appears not to. The reason for their differences is unknown.
        Cassini also found thin atmospheres around the moons Dione and Rhea—but we’re talking thin,
        around 5 trillion times less dense than at Earth’s surface. Hyperion can’t boast any sort of
        atmosphere, but the tumbling, sponge-looking moon does build up a static charge, which
        scientists realized when Cassini passed through a beam of electrons coming up from the
        moon’s surface. Hyperion is the only object in the solar system other than Earth’s moon
        that’s been confirmed as having a charged surface. Cassini also solved the centuries-old
        puzzle about why the moon Iapetus has one snow-white hemisphere while its other hemisphere
        is nearly as dark as charcoal. Iapetus is tidally locked, so it always shows the same side
        to Saturn, and one side always faces the direction in which it’s orbiting. It turns out that
        dark material falls on Iapetus’s leading side. “It’s coming actually from [the outer moon]
        Phoebe’s ring—it’s Phoebe dust,” Spilker said. The moon Phoebe creates one of Saturn’s
        rings, and Iapetus is flying through its debris. “Headed forward, you get all the bug
        splats,” Spilker said. At the same time, ice migrates to the poles, not by sliding but by
        sort of hopping, a molecule at a time. On the moon Tethys, Cassini observed mysterious red
        arcs, though they weren’t easy to see. “We didn’t even see them until a Cassini scientist
        started looking in the near-infrared,” Spilker said. In the infrared, the red arcs are
        obvious, as if someone dragged a giant red crayon across the surface of a golf ball. The
        arcs don’t appear to be related to any physical features of the moon’s surface, such as
        valleys or fractures. “They go up mountains and down into craters,” Spilker said. “But
        there’s no obvious fractures.” If the red arcs are coming from fractures, they’re too small
        to see at the resolution Cassini’s instruments provided. The arcs are also unevenly
        distributed on the moon’s surface. “It’s only the north,” Spilker said. “Why aren’t they in
        the south? It’s just sort of a late-mission mystery.” As scientists continue to analyze
        Cassini’s data, they will likely solve more mysteries about Saturn’s menagerie of moons,
        and they will almost certainly find more mysteries that need solving.
    </string>
    <!-- saturn moon enceladus information -->
    <string name="saturn_moon_enceladus">Enceladus</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_enceladus_text_box_1">
        The Voyager and Pioneer flybys of the 1970s and 1980s provided rough sketches of Saturn’s
        moons. But during its many years in Saturn orbit, NASA’s Cassini spacecraft discovered
        previously unknown moons, solved mysteries about known ones, studied their interactions
        with the rings and uncovered new mysteries—including the discovery on an ocean moon with
        potential ingredients for life—that will engage a whole new generation of space scientists.
        While the larger moons are spherical, others are shaped like a sweet potato (Prometheus),
        a regular potato (Pandora), a meatball (Janus), and even a sponge (Hyperion). Some have a
        gnarled, irregular shape and texture like a dirty ice-ball (Epimetheus). One object observed
        in the rings (and unofficially called Peggy) may be a moon forming or disintegrating, or it
        might not truly be a moon at all. Four spacecraft have visited the Saturn system, but
        Cassini alone actually orbited the ringed planet. Doing so bought Cassini time—more than
        a decade—to linger and watch Saturn’s exotic zoo of 60-plus moons like no spacecraft
        before. Cassini looked, listened, sniffed and even tasted Saturn’s moons, and what it
        learned about them is nothing less than extraordinary.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_enceladus_text_box_2">Habitability Outside the Habitability Zone</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_enceladus_text_box_3">
        Haze-enshrouded Titan is Saturn’s largest moon and the solar system’s second-largest, and
        an all-around exceptional place. Titan is the only known world other than Earth where any
        sort of liquid collects on its surface.
        Earth has liquid water oceans because it orbits within the solar system’s habitable zone,
        the range of distance from our sun that is neither so hot that oceans boil away nor so cold
        that they’re frozen. The Saturn system is far outside of the habitable zone, and Titan’s
        surface temperature is so cold that the moon’s surface is largely water ice instead of
        rock. But the temperature is just right for liquid methane and ethane. Cassini scientists
        found not only that liquid methane and ethane exist on Titan, but that they rain from the
        sky and fill liquid lakes, which are as wide as several hundred miles (or kilometers) and
        as deep as hundreds of feet (or meters). Despite Titan’s distance from the sun, Cassini
        also found evidence of a global (or at least regional) liquid water ocean below its frigid
        surface, but Titan isn’t the only Saturnian moon that boasts of a subsurface sea.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_enceladus_text_box_4">Ocean Moon</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_enceladus_text_box_5">
        Cassini scientists were astonished when they found a plume spraying water vapor, icy
        particles and simple organic materials into space from the south polar region of Enceladus.
        Scientists determined that the jets are the source of material for Saturn’s E-Ring. The
        jets spew out of great fissures, or cracks, known as “tiger stripes,” which Cassini
        scientists found grow wider or narrower depending on where Enceladus is in its orbit
        around Saturn. Observations of its gravity and the contents of the plume suggested that
        Enceladus almost certainly contains a subsurface liquid water ocean near its southern
        polar region. Now more and more Cassini data indicates that Enceladus is home to a global
        (not just regional) ocean, and the jets near the south polar region are powered by
        hotspots, where heat from the interior ocean escapes. On Earth, hydrothermal vents at the
        ocean floor can produce habitats where organisms can flourish, completely cut off from
        sunlight. Many scientists suspect that life on Earth might have begun around these undersea
        environments. The evidence is beginning to pile up that Enceladus might have hydrothermal
        vents too. But vents or no vents, the Cassini mission showed that Enceladus appears to have
        all the components necessary for life. The food component is methane, which has been
        observed in surprising abundance in the plume, said Bonnie Buratti, a senior research
        scientist at NASA’s Jet Propulsion Laboratory. “Water, food, and heat—everything is there
        for life as we know it,” she said. “It’s all there.” Even if Enceladus isn’t home to even
        simple organisms, the presence of the necessary conditions is itself a remarkable finding.
    </string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_enceladus_text_box_6">Moon Mysteries Managed</string>
    <string name="saturn_moon_enceladus_text_box_7">
        Enceladus and Titan get a lot of attention, but the Cassini mission also provided countless
        insights about dozens of Saturn’s other moons. The moon Mimas, whose Herschel Crater makes
        it look like the Death Star from "Star Wars," was thought to be an old, dead world,
        according to Cassini project scientist Linda Spilker. But Cassini scientists found
        evidence that it too may have a subsurface ocean, or at least a football-shaped water-ice
        core. “It’s curious. Mimas and Enceladus are the same size,” Spilker said, but Enceladus
        has water jets while Mimas appears not to. The reason for their differences is unknown.
        Cassini also found thin atmospheres around the moons Dione and Rhea—but we’re talking thin,
        around 5 trillion times less dense than at Earth’s surface. Hyperion can’t boast any sort of
        atmosphere, but the tumbling, sponge-looking moon does build up a static charge, which
        scientists realized when Cassini passed through a beam of electrons coming up from the
        moon’s surface. Hyperion is the only object in the solar system other than Earth’s moon
        that’s been confirmed as having a charged surface. Cassini also solved the centuries-old
        puzzle about why the moon Iapetus has one snow-white hemisphere while its other hemisphere
        is nearly as dark as charcoal. Iapetus is tidally locked, so it always shows the same side
        to Saturn, and one side always faces the direction in which it’s orbiting. It turns out that
        dark material falls on Iapetus’s leading side. “It’s coming actually from [the outer moon]
        Phoebe’s ring—it’s Phoebe dust,” Spilker said. The moon Phoebe creates one of Saturn’s
        rings, and Iapetus is flying through its debris. “Headed forward, you get all the bug
        splats,” Spilker said. At the same time, ice migrates to the poles, not by sliding but by
        sort of hopping, a molecule at a time. On the moon Tethys, Cassini observed mysterious red
        arcs, though they weren’t easy to see. “We didn’t even see them until a Cassini scientist
        started looking in the near-infrared,” Spilker said. In the infrared, the red arcs are
        obvious, as if someone dragged a giant red crayon across the surface of a golf ball. The
        arcs don’t appear to be related to any physical features of the moon’s surface, such as
        valleys or fractures. “They go up mountains and down into craters,” Spilker said. “But
        there’s no obvious fractures.” If the red arcs are coming from fractures, they’re too small
        to see at the resolution Cassini’s instruments provided. The arcs are also unevenly
        distributed on the moon’s surface. “It’s only the north,” Spilker said. “Why aren’t they in
        the south? It’s just sort of a late-mission mystery.” As scientists continue to analyze
        Cassini’s data, they will likely solve more mysteries about Saturn’s menagerie of moons,
        and they will almost certainly find more mysteries that need solving.
    </string>
    <!-- comet information -->
    <string name="comet">Comets</string>
    <string name="comet_text_box_1">
       In the distant past, people were both awed and alarmed by comets, perceiving them as
        long-haired stars that appeared in the sky unannounced and unpredictably. Chinese astronomers
        kept extensive records for centuries, including illustrations of characteristic types of
        comet tails, times of cometary appearances and disappearances, and celestial positions. These
        historic comet annals have proven to be a valuable resource for later astronomers. We now
        know that comets are leftovers from the dawn of our solar system around 4.6 billion years
        ago, and consist mostly of ice coated with dark organic material. They have been referred
        to as "dirty snowballs." They may yield important clues about the formation of our solar
        system. Comets may have brought water and organic compounds, the building blocks of life,
        to the early Earth and other parts of the solar system.
    </string>
    <string name="comet_text_box_2">Where Do Comets Come From?</string>
    <string name="comet_text_box_3">
       As theorized by astronomer Gerard Kuiper in 1951, a disc-like belt of icy bodies exists
        beyond Neptune, where a population of dark comets orbits the Sun in the realm of Pluto.
        These icy objects, occasionally pushed by gravity into orbits bringing them closer to the
        Sun, become the so-called short-period comets. Taking less than 200 years to orbit the Sun,
        in many cases their appearance is predictable because they have passed by before. Less
        predictable are long-period comets, many of which arrive from a region called the Oort
        Cloud about 100,000 astronomical units (that is, about 100,000 times the distance between
        Earth and the Sun) from the Sun. These Oort Cloud comets can take as long as 30 million
        years to complete one trip around the Sun. Each comet has a tiny frozen part, called a
        nucleus, often no larger than a few kilometers across. The nucleus contains icy chunks,
        frozen gases with bits of embedded dust. A comet warms up as it nears the Sun and develops
        an atmosphere, or coma. The Sun's heat causes the comet's ices to change to gases so the
        coma gets larger. The coma may extend hundreds of thousands of kilometers. The pressure of
        sunlight and high-speed solar particles (solar wind) can blow the coma dust and gas away
        from the Sun, sometimes forming a long, bright tail. Comets actually have two tails―a dust
        tail and an ion (gas) tail. Most comets travel a safe distance from the Sun―comet Halley
        comes no closer than 89 million kilometers (55 million miles). However, some comets, called
        sungrazers, crash straight into the Sun or get so close that they break up and evaporate.
    </string>
    <string name="comet_text_box_4">Exploration of Comets</string>
    <string name="comet_text_box_5">
        Scientists have long wanted to study comets in some detail, tantalized by the few 1986
        images of comet Halleys nucleus. NASAs Deep Space 1 spacecraft flew by comet Borrelly
        in 2001 and photographed its nucleus, which is about 8 kilometers (5 miles) long. NASAs
        Stardust mission successfully flew within 236 kilometers (147 miles) of the nucleus of
        Comet Wild 2 in January 2004, collecting cometary particles and interstellar dust for a
        sample return to Earth in 2006. The photographs taken during this close flyby of a comet
        nucleus show jets of dust and a rugged, textured surface. Analysis of the Stardust samples
        suggests that comets may be more complex than originally thought. Minerals formed near the
        Sun or other stars were found in the samples, suggesting that materials from the inner
        regions of the solar system traveled to the outer regions where comets formed. Another NASA
        mission, Deep Impact, consisted of a flyby spacecraft and an impactor. In July 2005, the
        impactor was released into the path of the nucleus of comet Tempel 1 in a planned collision,
        which vaporized the impactor and ejected massive amounts of fine, powdery material from
        beneath the comet's surface. En route to impact, the impactor camera imaged the comet in
        increasing detail. Two cameras and a spectrometer on the flyby spacecraft recorded the
        dramatic excavation that helped determine the interior composition and structure of the
        nucleus. After their successful primary missions, the Deep Impact spacecraft and the Stardust
        spacecraft were still healthy and were retargeted for additional cometary flybys.
        Deep Impact's mission, EPOXI (Extrasolar Planet Observation and Deep Impact Extended
        Investigation), comprised two projects: the Deep Impact Extended Investigation (DIXI),
        which encountered comet Hartley 2 in November 2010, and the Extrasolar Planet Observation
        and Characterization (EPOCh) investigation, which searched for Earth-size planets around
        other stars on route to Hartley 2. NASA returned to comet Tempel 1 in 2011, when the
        Stardust New Exploration of Tempel 1 (NExT) mission observed changes in the nucleus since
        Deep Impact's 2005 encounter.
    </string>
    <string name="comet_text_box_6">How Comets Get Their Names</string>
    <string name="comet_text_box_7">
        Comet naming can be complicated. Comets are generally named for their discoverer—either a
        person or a spacecraft. This International Astronomical Union guideline was developed only
        in the last century. For example, comet Shoemaker-Levy 9 was so named because it was the
        ninth short-periodic comet discovered by Eugene and Carolyn Shoemaker and David Levy. Since
        spacecraft are very effective at spotting comets many comets have LINEAR, SOHO or WISE in
        their names.
    </string>
    <!-- asteroids information -->
    <string name="asteroids">Asteroids</string>
    <string name="asteroids_text_box_1">
       Asteroids, sometimes called minor planets, are rocky remnants left over from the early
        formation of our solar system about 4.6 billion years ago. Most of this ancient space
        rubble can be found orbiting the sun between Mars and Jupiter within the main asteroid belt.
        Asteroids range in size from Vesta—the largest at about 329 miles (530 kilometers) in
        diameter - to bodies that are less than 33 feet (10 meters) across. The total mass of all
        the asteroids combined is less than that of Earths Moon. Most asteroids are irregularly
        shaped, though a few are nearly spherical, and they are often pitted or cratered. As they
        revolve around the sun in elliptical orbits, the asteroids also rotate, sometimes quite
        erratically, tumbling as they go. More than 150 asteroids are known to have a small
        companion moon (some have two moons). There are also binary (double) asteroids, in which
        two rocky bodies of roughly equal size orbit each other, as well as triple asteroid systems
    </string>
    <string name="asteroids_text_box_2">Composition</string>
    <string name="asteroids_text_box_3">
       The three broad composition classes of asteroids are C-, S-, and M-types. The C-type
        (chondrite) asteroids are most common, probably consist of clay and silicate rocks, and
        are dark in appearance. They are among the most ancient objects in the solar system. The
        S-types ("stony") are made up of silicate materials and nickel-iron. The M-types are
        metallic (nickel-iron). The asteroids compositional differences are related to how far from
        the sun they formed. Some experienced high temperatures after they formed and partly melted,
        with iron sinking to the center and forcing basaltic (volcanic) lava to the surface.
        Jupiters massive gravity and occasional close encounters with Mars or another object change
        the asteroids orbits, knocking them out of the main belt and hurling them into space in
        all directions across the orbits of the other planets. Stray asteroids and asteroid fragments
        slammed into Earth and the other planets in the past, playing a major role in altering the
        geological history of the planets and in the evolution of life on Earth. Scientists
        continuously monitor Earth-crossing asteroids, whose paths intersect Earth's orbit, and
        near-Earth asteroids that approach Earth's orbital distance to within about 45 million
        kilometers (28 million miles) and may pose an impact danger. Radar is a valuable tool in
        detecting and monitoring potential impact hazards. By reflecting transmitted signals off
        objects, images and other information can be derived from the echoes. Scientists can learn
        a great deal about an asteroid's orbit, rotation, size, shape, and metal concentration.
    </string>
    <string name="asteroids_text_box_4">Asteroid Classifications</string>
    <string name="asteroids_text_box_5">
        Main Asteroid Belt: The majority of known asteroids orbit within the asteroid belt between
        Mars and Jupiter, generally with not very elongated orbits. The belt is estimated to contain
        between 1.1 and 1.9 million asteroids larger than 1 kilometer (0.6 mile) in diameter, and
        millions of smaller ones. Early in the history of the solar system, the gravity of newly
        formed Jupiter brought an end to the formation of planetary bodies in this region and caused
        the small bodies to collide with one another, fragmenting them into the asteroids we observe
        today. Trojans: These asteroids share an orbit with a larger planet, but do not collide
        with it because they gather around two special places in the orbit (called the L4 and L5
        Lagrangian points). There, the gravitational pull from the sun and the planet are balanced
        by a trojan's tendency to otherwise fly out of the orbit. The Jupiter trojans form the most
        significant population of trojan asteroids. It is thought that they are as numerous as the
        asteroids in the asteroid belt. There are Mars and Neptune trojans, and NASA announced the
        discovery of an Earth trojan in 2011. Near-Earth Asteroids: These objects have orbits that
        pass close by that of Earth. Asteroids that actually cross Earth's orbital path are known
        as Earth-crossers. As of June 19, 2013, 10,003 near-Earth asteroids are known and the number
        over 1 kilometer in diameter is thought to be 861, with 1,409 classified as potentially
        hazardous asteroids - those that could pose a threat to Earth.
    </string>
    <string name="asteroids_text_box_6">How Asteroids Get Their Names</string>
    <string name="asteroids_text_box_7">
        The International Astronomical Unions Committee on Small Body Nomenclature.is a little less
        strict when it comes to naming asteroids than other IAU naming committees. So out there
        orbiting the sun we have giant space rocks named for Mr. Spock (a cat named for the character
        of "Star Trek" fame), rock musician Frank Zappa, beloved teachers such as Florida’s
        Cynthia L. Reyes, and more somber tributes such as the seven asteroids named for the crew
        of the Space Shuttle Columbia killed in 2003. Asteroids are also named for places and a
        variety of other things. (The IAU discourages naming asteroids for pets, so Mr. Spock
        stands alone). Asteroids are also given a number, for example (99942) Apophis. The Harvard
        Smithsonian Center for Astrophysics keeps a fairly current list of asteroid names.
    </string>
    <!-- pluto information -->
    <string name="pluto">Pluto</string>
    <string name="pluto_text_box_1">
       Pluto is a complex and mysterious world with mountains, valleys, plains, craters, and maybe
        glaciers. Discovered in 1930, Pluto was long considered our solar systems ninth planet.
        But after the discovery of similar intriguing worlds deeper in the distant Kuiper Belt, icy
        Pluto was reclassified as a dwarf planet. Pluto is orbited by five known moons, the largest
        of which is Charon. Charon is about half the size of Pluto itself, making it the largest
        satellite relative to the planet it orbits in our solar system. Pluto and Charon are often
        referred to as a "double planet." Pluto is named after the Roman god of the underworld.
    </string>
    <string name="pluto_text_box_2">Size and Distance</string>
    <string name="pluto_text_box_3">
       With a radius of 715 miles (1,151 kilometers), Pluto is about 1/6 the width of Earth. If
        Earth was the size of a nickel, Pluto would be about as big as a popcorn kernel. From an
        average distance of 3.7 billion miles (5.9 billion kilometers), Pluto is 39 astronomical
        units away from the sun. One astronomical unit (abbreviated as AU), is the distance from
        the sun to Earth. From this distance, it takes sunlight 5.5 hours to travel from the sun
        to Pluto. If you were to stand on the surface of Pluto at noon, the sun would be 1/900 the
        brightness it is here on Earth, or about 300 times as bright as our full moon. There is a
        moment each day near sunset here on Earth when the light is the same brightness as midday
        on Pluto. Find out when you can experience "Pluto time" where you live.
    </string>
    <string name="pluto_text_box_4">Orbit and Rotation</string>
    <string name="pluto_text_box_5">
        Plutos orbit around the sun is unusual compared to the planets: its both elliptical and
        tilted. Plutos 248-year-long, oval-shaped orbit can take it as far as 49.3 astronomical
        units (AU) from the sun, and as close as 30 AU. (One AU is the mean distance between Earth
        and the sun: about 93 million miles or 150 million kilometers.) But on average, Pluto is 3.7
        billion miles (5.9 billion kilometers) away from the sun, or 39 AU. From 1979 to 1999,
        Pluto was near perihelion, when it is closest to the sun. During this time, Pluto was
        actually closer to the sun than Neptune. One day on Pluto takes about 153 hours. Its axis
        of rotation is tilted 57 degrees with respect to the plane of its orbit around the sun, so
        it spins almost on its side. Pluto also exhibits a retrograde rotation; spinning from east
        to west like Venus and Uranus.
    </string>
    <string name="pluto_text_box_6">Formation</string>
    <string name="pluto_text_box_7">
        Dwarf planet Pluto is a member of a group of objects that orbit in a disc-like zone beyond
        the orbit of Neptune called the Kuiper Belt. This distant realm is populated with thousands
        of miniature icy worlds, which formed early in the history of our solar system about 4.5
        billion years ago. These icy, rocky bodies are called Kuiper Belt objects, transneptunian
        objects, or plutoids.
    </string>
</resources>